http://professional-products.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Log In
My Cart:
0 item(s)
Timing Pointers
Search:
Search
Professional Products
Categories
AN PlumbingFuel Inlet & Return FittingsAN Tube Nuts & SleevesFlare ReducerFuel Pressure Take OffAN Flare CapsStraight Hose End45 Swivel End90 Swivel Hose EndAN Fittings - BlackFuel Pump & Regulator FittingsAN Bulkhead FittingsNPT Pipe PlugsAN Fittings - Red & BlueAN Fittings - PolishedStraight HoseAir & Fuel DeliveryIntake ManifoldsSmall Block ChevyBig Block ChevyLS1-LS2-LS6Small Block Ford4.6L Ford318-340-360 ChryslerManifold AccessoriesThrottle BodiesFord 4.6 1996-2004Ford 5.0 & 4.6 1986-2004Chevy TPI 1985-1992Chevy LT1 1992-1997Chevy LS1 and LS2Ford V6 & V8 2005-2010Acura 1994-2001 GSR/Type RFuel FiltersMechanical Fuel PumpsElectric Fuel PumpsFuel InletsFuel Pressure RegulatorsCarbureted RegulatorsEFI RegulatorsFuel RailsFuel System FittingsFuel Line KitsGaugesDampersPowerforce Street DampersSmall Block ChevyBig Block ChevyLS ChevySmall Block FordBig Block Ford4.6L FordMOPARPontiacOldsmobileJeepAMCHonda-AcuraNissanPowerforce Plus SFI Race DampersSmall Block ChevyBig Block ChevyLS ChevySmall Block FordBig Block Ford4.6L & Coyote FordMOPARPontiacOldsmobileHonda-AcuraAMCNissanDamper AccessoriesTiming PointersSlate SeriesIgnition Powerfire IPowerfire IIPowerfire IV CDI Ignition BoxCoils & Ignition AccessoriesHEI DistributorsOil FiltersPP SaleGaskets & HardwareManifold GasketsThrottle Body GasketsBolts
AN Plumbing
Fuel Inlet & Return Fittings
AN Tube Nuts & Sleeves
Flare Reducer
Fuel Pressure Take Off
AN Flare Caps
Straight Hose End
45 Swivel End
Password *
Forgot Password ?
Login
or registration
×
Registration
Profile Informations
First Name *
Last Name *
Subscribe to Newsletter
or login
First name is required!
Last name is required!
First name is not valid!
Last name is not valid!
This is not an email address!
Email address is required!
This email is already registered!
Password is required!
Enter a valid password!
Please enter 6 or more characters!
Please enter 16 or less characters!
Passwords are not same!
Terms and Conditions are required!
Email or Password is wrong!
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Professional Products uses and protects any information
that you give Professional Products when you use this website.
Professional Products is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website,
then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Professional Products may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.
By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. These practices may be changed at any time without notice.
Professional Products also owns several other domain names that may point to Professional-Products.com, and we may from time to time establish new websites controlled by us. This policy applies only to Professional-Products.com and other websites we control posting this policy, but not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link and Professional Products cannot and does not guarantee the security of any personal information disclosed on those sites.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website
according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure,
we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure
the information we collect online.
Web Site Registration
In order to use some features of this Web site, users must first complete the registration form. During registration, users are required to give their contact information (name and e-mail address). This information is used to contact users about the topics on our site for which they have expressed interest and to enable users to retrieve lost passwords. It is optional for the user to provide other requested demographic information.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic
and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical
analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful
and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Accepting cookies while on Professional-Products.com will not put the user at risk for marketing to other sites.
Web Statistics
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use for reporting and sponsorship purposes. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to third parties your information. This excludes trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as they agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to
12600 Daphne Avenue
Hawthorne, CA 90250.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Notification of Changes
Professional Products reserves the right to makes changes in our Online Privacy Statement from time to time. If a material change is made to this Online Privacy Statement, we will post a notice of change on our website. Your continued use of our website will signify your acceptance of these changes.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Go!
©
2015 Professional Products. All Rights Reserved.
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Website Design, Black Ink Media
